-Bala, are you alright?
-I'm fine.
I'm fine.
-Gonca, are you alright? -I'm fine.
Didn't I kill you?
I cut you into pieces with my sword.
I threw you off the castle walls.
How is that possible?
How did you not die?
You demon with nine lives!
I'm here to finish
what I started, Osman.
The ground didn't accept you, huh?
I will bury you deep under the ground!
You will go under the ground, Osman.
I will make you go through...
...much worse than what you did to me.
I will...
...kill all of your family...
...one by one in pain.
First me before my family.
You have to get me first.
You vile dog.
Come here. Come.
You know what my sword tastes like,
...Sofia.
It won't be that easy, Osman.
-You will kneel this time. Soldiers!
-Alps! Attack!
Ya Allah
Bala, aren't you curious
about the secret I'll give you?
Keep your poisonous words to yourself, demon!
You won't live long this time.
I will kill you.
Praise be to my hatun. Come on!
I killed you.
You just don't know yet.
I'm here, mother!
Sofia...
Sofia, we need to go. We're losing.
What are you doing, Lukas? What?
Our soldiers are dying
-He has to die!
Yes, but not now!
If we stay, we'll lose! Let's go!
He has to die! He has to!
-Sofia!
Osman.
They're running off.
-They can't go anywhere.
-Let's go.
-Gonca, are you alright? -I'm fine.
Good. Come on!
Allah is the greatest!
Gonca!
Begum Hatun...
Thank you.
Thank you, Begum Hatun.
I owe you a life now.
There's the sake of fight
between you and me.
So you owe me nothing.
Alaaddin!
Go after our father! Go!
Alright, brother!
Come on, alps! Let's go!
Come on, alps!
-Is everyone alright?
-I'm fine, my Bey.
I'm good, my Shahzade.
Dastards who ambushed
Borus got what they deserved
Everyone is fine.
Thanks to Allah.
Alps, inform all the alps around Sogut.
Tell them to hold all the ways going
to the borders of Prusa and Byzantine.
-All of them.
-As you order, my Bey.
Let's go.
Sofia, you survived this time.
But you're walking to your death again.
-Osman. Osman!
Bala.
Bala, you have a wound.
What is this, Bala?
Bala. Bala.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why are you coming with us?
Alps, bring some bandages.
Give it to me. Come on, come on.
Oh Bala...
Lukas.
We were supposed to kill Kayi women
here while Osman was chasing a lie.
We were so close.
I swear both Osman and Bala
will regret that they didn't die today.
I will open a wound inside them
which is sharper than a sword.
They will beg me for mercy.
I know this wild look that would
scare even the devil himself.
I have a treasure which
is very valuable for Kayis...
...and which only I know about, Lukas.
Even the name of this treasure
will make Kayis kneel before me.
What is it, Sofia?
The chain I will put around
the neck of Kayis, Lukas.
Be patient, though.
You will see soon.
Let's not stay long here.
They may come any moment.
They must have held the road to the castle.
-You should use the other ways.
-You?
-Are you not coming?
-I will.
But I have a thing to do first.
The devil...
...who we thought was dead for so long.
Osman.
You killed Sofia with your own hands.
-Right.
All the cruelty she caused is
clear from the way she hid her face.
But she got out of hell.
She kept her grudge alive and
she is making plans against us.
She brought trouble...
...as soon as she came to the frontiers.
First Baysungur and his men...
...then Fatma.
Then you.
She knows well that if she touches my
daughter or you, I will cut her into pieces.
But remember.
She is not just an enemy.
Now she will attack us like a mad dog.
Come on, my Bey.
Let's go after her, let's go and kill her.
Bala, how can we do that?
No. Don't you see your wound?
First, your wound will heal.
Alright? You will be alright...
...then you will stand next to me.
-Alright.
-Bala...
She got out of hell...
She revived in fiery flames.
But we will drown her in her own blood.
We will drown her in her blood.
Son.
Come.
Mother, are you alright?
Come, check your mother's wounds.
-I am alright, my son.
I am alright.
No. No. We have to do something.
You've lost blood.
You will get weaker.
Let's go. Come on. -Come on.
Hold it here.
Hold this here.
My Bey..
We killed all the infidels.
But their owners... Did they run away, my Bey?
Neither they nor Karesi Bey...
None of them can escape
our wrath. None of them.
For sure, my Bey.
But...
That dog named Sofia...
Her mind works like the devil's.
Thus, we won't rush.
First, we will make our plan.
-Then we will set out.
-Yes my Bey. -Come on.
His wound is serious, and
he has lost a lot of blood.
Prepare the hot water.
Prepare the ointments! Come on!
Father!
Father! My father is
bleeding! My father is dying!
Father, don't die, father!
I am alright, my daughter.
My father is dying!
-Ayse... Ayse come.
Come, your father will be alright.
-My father is bleeding.
My father is dying, Fatma
sister! My father is dying!
Alright Ayse, come. Let's go out.
Father, don't leave me alone!
Don't leave me alone, father!
Don't be afraid, my daughter.
Don't be afraid, I will be alright.
-Ayse, come with me.
Come, they will treat your father. Come on.
-Father...
My mother left... Now
you... Don't leave me father!
Father!
Father don't die!
-Ayse, come on!
Let's go out, so your father
can recover. Come on.
Father...
Come on.
My knights.
Every soldier raised in this
temple will bring hell to the Turks!
Go on
My most valuable weapon.
That's enough, Poena.
Enough?
Do you want me to show
mercy to your soldiers, aunt?
Or should I continue with you?
Don't show mercy.
The one before you is not me but
Osman, the killer of your parents...
...and Bala.
Osman and Bala.
They will both die, aunt.
May it be good, God willing.
Who are you?
My Halime's amulet...
Halime, is that you?
My Halime!
Wait!
Wait! Are you here, my daughter?
My Halime!
Is it you, my daughter?
Are you here, my daughter? Wait! Don't go!
Stop!
Don't leave your mother!
Halime!
Stop!
Let me see your face for once!
For once, my daughter!
Bala!
-Mother, are you alright?
-Mother...
Why are you crying? Does it hurt badly?
I am alright.
Thanks to Allah.
I had a dream...
Dream...
You'll be alright, mother.
Is that all the anger you have for
Osman, the killer of your family?
You are perfect my little bird.
I will take Osman's heart
out with my own hands, aunt.
You're amazing, my little bird.
My Halime...
Let's welcome our guests now, right?
May it be easy Hatuns.
Thank you Bala Hatun.
-May it be easy.
Welcome to our lands.
Come, my beautiful daughter.
Let's help them. Come on.
Give that to me.
Here.
Praise be. Praise be.
Our Osman Bey is on a conquest.
But we brought you his greetings.
Peace be upon him.
From now on, our land is your land.
Our food is your food.
Thank you Bala Hatun.
You stole my future.
And I will wipe out your
lineage with your blood.
Come, Halime.
-Is the child ready? Everything is ready.
-Do they look alike?
-Yes.
We attacked the caravan
heading to the headquarters.
The news will arrive soon.
We've waited for this day for so long.
You know very well what to do.
You will distract the cook
and you take the child.
Say goodbye to your daughter, Bala.
Come on. Now.
Come on.
Come my daughter. Ulgen.
My Bala.
How's the food? It's ready, isn't it?
Don't worry, Bala.
I cooked enough for everyone.
Make sure there's nothing
missing for our guests.
Don't worry.
Alright. -Bala Hatun.
Bala Hatun, they attacked the
caravan heading to the headquarters.
What?
Bring the horses! Now!
Ulgen, when you're done, go back to Yenisehir.
I entrust my Halime to you, alright?
-Alright, Bala.
My daughter, wait for
me, I'll come back, alright?
Ulgen, come on
Mother, don't go!
My Halime, my beautiful daughter,
I will go but I will come back.
Come on, my daughter. Come on.
-My dear...
Bring it here. Here!
Come on!
Come on
She will come, my dear.
Don't worry.
She will come back.
You look like you're about to give birth.
How much time is left?
His father is at war.
I will wait until he returns.
You stir it.
-Alright.
Halime...
Ulgen Hatun, help!
Allah
Damn...
Stop, you will burn yourself!
Halime.
Hi.
Do you want..
Your mother is waiting for you, Halime.
She said Halime should
come, yes, Halime should come.
She said she'll take you with her.
You will come?
My good girl.
Good girl. Come. Come.
Now you are mine, little demon.
Where is my mother?
You little demon...
You sleep, my daughter...
Throw the shoes by the river.
Dress the child in her clothes. Then go and
report that the child fell in the river.
Days later...
...when they find the child
they will be sure anyway.
Come on.
Can I take my revenge now?
When the time comes,
you will take your revenge.
My beautiful Poena.
I live on that dream, aunt.
My little bird.
But how much longer do I have to wait, aunt?
I must go now.
You will take good care of my Poena.
I'll come again very soon.
Aunt...
I don't want to wait any
longer. Let me come with you.
You see...
I'm ready.
I'm strong.
I can fight.
I want to see the killers of
my family, Osman and Bala...
...my enemies now, aunt.
Your greatest strength...
...will be your patience, my little bird.
That's what we said.
Rest well tonight.
Tomorrow morning.
Be ready at the castle.
My Bala.
I am alright.
Come.
Cerkutay.
My Bey.
Increase the precautions.
No one will be around the tribe.
As you order, my Bey.
How's Ilbay's condition, Turhan?
-He's better.
They treated his wound, my
Bey. He's in the healing tent.
Okay. Now
I go and see him.
Then we will organize the council.
Invite all the Beys.
-Yes my Bey.
Bring some sherbet...
I'm too thirsty...
Orhan.
Ilbay.
My Bey..
You are alright, huh?
I am alright, my Bey. I am.
I cauterized my wound in the forest myself.
The healer also took care of me, thank him.
The news you risked your life to deliver...
..saved Bala's life. Thank you.
Sure, my Bey.
But my Bey...
The only thing I learned from those infidels...
...is not just about the
attack on Bala Hatun.
What else?
Karesi Bey.
He has advanced his alliance with them...
...to the point of selling
steel to the infidels.
What are you saying?
Selling steel to the infidels?
Selling the essence of the
weapon that hits the hand of a Turk..
...to the infidels?
Karesi Bey.
Your hostility towards us...
...has made you this low, huh?
My Bey, we must do
whatever it takes to stop this.
We will.
Of course, we will.
Those Sofia's snakes...
Do they stay in Akhisar Castle?
-My Bey...
..from what I heard from Sofia's men...
...they hide in a temple.
Where is this temple?
I could not learn that, my Bey.
But the horses of those men who
came to the castle were never tired.
It seems the place is not far from Akhisar.
Orhan. -My Bey. -Tomorrow...
You will observe all the
temples around Akhisar.
You will find out where Sofia's snakes are.
As you say, my Bey.
Since you are well...
...regain your strength. From now on...
...you will stay with us.
As you say, my Bey.
You have nine lives, Lukas.
You survived Osman's clutches again.
He survived, not me.
If he hadn't arrived just in
time, we'd have killed his wife.
But she turned out to be lucky.
We shouldn't mess with
women and children, Lukas.
I want war and blood.
I will disgrace Osman on the battlefield.
We will, Karesi Bey.
Together, we will.
As I said before,
...my army needs steel. Osman
destroyed my mine, you know.
Is everything ready?
Yes, yes.
I got it brought from the castle of
Karadin that Osman gave to me.
We'll hit him with his own weapon, huh?
I already hit him.
I put a snake inside Osman's tent.
It is such a snake that...
...it will let me know about
Osman's every step and breath.
You got one of his beys, huh?
Yes, yes.
But I have one more person
that I've wanted to get for so long.
Someone precious.
And I don't want her to
be hurt when the war starts.
Who?
Which one?
Lukas.
And Karesi Bey who collaborates with him.
And..
The demon called Sofia...
...who came across me again.
The number of our enemies
is increasing day by day.
We have three fronts at war.
While there are so many heathens who want
to break our claws and disgrace our state,
...Muslims should never..
...ever make any mistakes.
You should...
...know that well.
We will stay in our land in peace and order.
So everybody should do...
...their duties with more care.
Now tell me.
Begum Hatun.
What's the condition of the
merchants and local people?
Does anyone have a problem?
They have no problems, my Bey.
Merchants are pleased to trade in our market.
Okay, okay.
You tell me, Gencer Bey.
What's the situation in Mekece?
Are your alps...
...cautious?
We took all the measures, my Bey.
The castle is safe, for sure.
But...
I don't understand one thing, Osman Bey.
Someone told Karesi Bey about our hunting plan.
I thought you'd bring up the subject, but...
...we're talking about the market and Mekece.
This council is the secret center of the state.
If there is someone you suspect among us,
...expose him right here right now.
Otherwise, none of us can stand
with our heads up before you.
Gencer Bey is right, my Bey.
Even if there is little suspicion,
...we should arrest the
traitor and have a trial.
I talked to Karesi...
...just to bait him.
If he were working with a traitor among us
...he would have shown his true color.
Well... It seems he found out
about the hunting plan by observing.
You should know this.
I fully trust my beys in the
council and my alps in the army!
Otherwise...
...we wouldn't be talking
about the state affairs here.
From now on, while performing their duties,
...everybody will be more careful and cautious.
You may leave.
One of them is betraying us.
We will find out who.
We will talk about that now.
One of the merchants left this
saying it's important, Begum Hatun.
He's looking for a traitor even in his shadow.
And you send me a message to meet?
I know what to do.
Prepare my horse.
You said you fully trust them in the council.
You did that to clear their
suspicion, huh, my Bey?
Yes. Yes.
Well..
Being a state is something like this.
Begum, Bayhan or Gencer.
One of them betrayed us and the state.
Whoever is that vile dog,
...we will find evidence and expose.
And we will punish.
Boran. Cerkutay. This is my order.
-My Bey.
You'll always keep your eyes on them.
You will tell me about every step they take.
As you order, my Bey.
The jackal who eats the council
up and exposes the state's secrets...
...will be revealed soon, brother.
Brother.
The traitor in the council...
...is Begum Hatun. I'm sure of that.
She made mistakes over and over again.
I have the same name in my mind.
Where do you think she's going?
-To Karesi?
-We'll find out.
Let's go.
While Orhan is looking for the dog's nest,
the temple where Sofia's soldiers hide in,
...we will land our punch
at Karesi Bey who sells
steel to heathens and
forgets he's a Turk himself.
We'll hit him where he betrays.
We'll hit him with the steel
that he sends to the heathens.
This is the moment of truth, brother.
That's Karesi coming.
Traitor! Vile traitor.
We always get in trouble
as we have a traitor inside.
-The punishment will be so harsh.
-It will be.
It will be.
Welcome, Begum Hatun.
I'm not welcome, Karesi Bey.
I have things to tell you.
But first you tell me why you invited me.
I want to save you from the flames of the fire.
I invited you for this, Begum Hatun.
I've managed on my own so far.
So I expect help from nobody.
Don't contact me again, Karesi Bey.
Well... You asked me to pledge loyalty to you.
You keep sending notes
and gifts. But it's enough.
You asked me to wear this
necklace when I offer my loyalty.
But I won't offer my loyalty to you.
Don't come to me with such an offer again.
I care about your life, Begum Hatun.
You're on the wrong side.
But..
It's your choice.
Keep the necklace as a memory.
I understand you.
Stay safe.
What's going on here?
Ulgen!
Ulgen, what's going on here?
Ulgen?
I couldn't protect.
Protect what?
-I couldn't.
I couldn't.
Ulgen, where is Halime? Where is Halime?
-She fell.
-Where is she?
I couldn't find her.
Search everywhere!
Halime! Halime!
My daughter!
My dear... Search
everywhere! Search everywhere!
Search everywhere!
Halime!
No! Halime!
No! Halime! My dear!
My dear!
Halime.
My beautiful daughter.
Bala.
What's going on?
Your wound is opened again.
Your heart is hurting, right?
This pain never ends.
That's why I can't say anything
about Gonca's suffering.
No words could fit.
I can't say her grief would end.
Don't cry inside. Come to me.
Come to me.
Here, you can cry as much as you want.
You had the same dream again?
I saw Halime again.
She's grown up.
With her silky long hair.
I ran after her but I couldn't arrive in time.
I couldn't see her face.
-Close your eyes.
Her eyes are just like yours.
Her hair is long just like yours.
She takes after her mother.
Osman.
Sofia told me such a thing...
...that I can't help
thinking about it.
What did she say?
"I'll tell you such a
thing without killing you...
...that you'll beg me to live", she said.
Sofia knows both of us well.
She knows we won't bow against her.
What can be...
...the secret which can
make us bow against her?
My almighty God.
I'm begging you to let me
take revenge on those...
...evil Turks who stole
my family and childhood.
Give me strength to kill Osman,
Bala, their children, all of them.
My suffering can be relieved only in this way.
This great hole inside me...
...will be filled as they bleed.
Amen.
With a tiny piece of information, Karesi
Bey made Osman a prey during his own hunt.
Who knows what he can do to him when
he learns about Osman's new decisions?
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
Aykurt, Is our Bey in his tent?
Yes, Boran Bey.
Brother, hold these.
Thanks. Come on.
Do I have permission, my Bey?
Come in.
-My Bey.
-Are there any updates?
Begum Hatun and Karesi Bey met, my Bey.
It seems they've been
communicating for a long time, my Bey.
You say so? Where is she now?
-On the way, my Bey.
She'll arrive soon.
What did they talk about?
That's the main concern, my Bey.
Where have you been, sister?
You left without telling anyone.
What's the matter?
Are you questioning your sister now?
You should have told me at least.
I'd have told you if you
had needed to know, brother.
-Hey!
-What is this, Aykurt Cavus?
We're here with Osman
Bey's orders, Begum Hatun.
Your betrayal to the state and
Osman Bey has been exposed.
It's time for punishment.
Sisters! Alps! Take her.
-You're making a mistake.
-Aykurt Cavus!
This is Osman Bey's order.
Raise no difficulties. Come on.
I didn't betray Osman Bey! I didn't!
It's foggy.
We'll go there and be back quickly
without drawing any suspicion.
Where are you going so late, Gencer Bey?
What is this at this hour, my Bey?
O people
Osman Bey's orders!
Everybody gather in the square!
Shortly we will know if it's good or not.
Obviously, something big will
happen at this late hour of the night.
Attention! Osman Bey!
O people!
My house, my beys and sisters...
We've been looking for a traitor in
the council and tribe for a long time.
And now...
And now we know who the traitor is.
The traitor who looks like one of
us, tells the enemy our secrets...
...and collaborates with
Karesi Bey behind my back...
...is Begum Hatun.
Bring her.
You will be tried Begum Hatun.
Osman Bey, I...
Search her clothes.
A pearl necklace, a pearl necklace.
That really suits Karesi Bey.
Did Karesi Bey gift this to you?
-Yes, my Bey, but...
My Osman Bey...
...my sister would never betray you.
Let her explain herself. -No.
Cerkutay Bey...
...and Boran Bey...
...saw and heard everything...
...while watching Begum Hatun.
The evidence of betrayal..
...is this pearl necklace gifted by Karesi Bey.
My Bey, that's not how it happened. -No!
Enough
Betrayal cannot be explained.
You will stand trial...
...and be judged.
Yusuf Bey...
...we will investigate whether you are...
...involved in this.
Until Begum Hatun stands trial...
...you will be under watch in the tribe.
Take her to the caged tent.
Sister.
Come on.
Finally, Begum Hatun's
true face has been revealed.
I think Yusuf is also involved in this.
Being under watch is not enough for him.
Now, even if Yusuf catches
a bird with his mouth...
...he won't be able to
get close to Fatma Hatun.
Use this situation well, my son.
Come on.
Come here, Gunkurt.
Osman must have sent his Alps after me.
I cannot leave now.
Go to Karesi and tell him.
Tell him Begum Hatun was caught. But...
Be careful... Alright? Go.
Yes my Bey.
Get ready!
My Bey..
Wait!
I'll come with you
Father!
I told you to get well soon but I
didn't think it would be this soon.
Resting does not suit a Turk, my Bey.
Even if I stay, my blood will boil inside me.
Fair enough.
My dear.
Come on, to horses!
May your fight bring victory, Bey.
Thank you Bala, thank you.
Come on, let's go to the Sogut marketplace.
Mother, can I come to
the Sogut marketplace too?
I get bored here.
Besides, you'll be with me there.
Alright. Come.
But you will not leave my side for a second!
Where is Gonca?
I don't know.
Call her now, we have
to go. Let's not waste time.
You go and bring her.
Come on.
Gonca Hatun.
Get out.
I have things to talk about with Begum Hatun.
-Do you also believe I am a traitor?
-Aren't you?
Don't, Gonca..
Why would I betray Osman Bey?
I believe you.
You would not betray my father.
Because you love him, Begum Hatun.
Gonca Hatun.
What...
What are you saying?
It's not true...
-Whoever said it..
Will you call it a lie now, Begum?
I heard it from you, not someone else.
Don't...
Don't tell anyone..
What you're doing is very wrong.
But...
...staying here while
you are innocent is unfair.
Therefore, I will talk to my mother and father.
I will tell them everything.
Gonca..
If you tell something to someone...
...I won't be able to
look at their faces again.
It's time, Hatun.
Bala Hatun and the others will
soon leave to go to the marketplace.
Good.
Come on Gulce.
Please, Gonca, listen to me and don't do it!
Akhisar Castle
Karesi's steel caravan will be here shortly.
This will be the biggest and...
...grandest agreement of Byzantium.
Sofia.
-Stop.
Karesi is giving the Turks' most
valuable treasure to their eternal enemies.
Lukas...
With this agreement, history will be rewritten.
Imagine...
The miraculous steel that strengthens the
Turks' swords and brings them victories...
...will become a merciless weapon..
...in the hands of...
...Byzantine blacksmiths.
Once those weapons come
together with my own weapon...
...we will become the Turks' nightmare, Lukas.
That secret...
Sofia...
Aren't you really going to tell me?
Osman and Bala's daughter.
I have her.
Halime, whom everyone thought was dead.
Halime.
Halime...
...is my niece Poena, Lukas.
How?
I kidnapped her years ago and
convinced them that she was dead.
Bala has been crying at the grave of
a girl she never knew for years.
Did you turn Osman's own
daughter against her family?
You are the devil itself, Sofia.
Aunt.
Welcome, my little bird.
Meet Commander Lukas.
I am glad to meet you Poena.
It's an honour to meet you Commander Lukas.
That honour belongs to me.
The day you waited for has come.
You will go to Sogut...
...to meet your enemies.
Boran.
Yes?
Brother.
Did we not become a state?
We did, brother.
Why does my Bey come to every battle with us?
Could we not have raided this place ourselves?
Why did he not sit on
his chair and give orders?
But no... -Brother...
Look, state matters do not work like that.
You know the state matters, brother.
Brother, let me answer.
Did you understand what I said?
How do state matters work
then? You always know everything!
Cerkutay, brother...
What is going on there?
What are you whispering about?
Come on, say it so we can hear it.
My Bey.
Boran is asking why our Bey
comes with us to every battle.
He says we could have
raided this place ourselves.
He says you could have just sat
on your chair and given orders.
I also do not understand why he says that.
What are you saying, you mad man?
So Boran says that, huh?
Yes, my Bey.
Boran says that, but you
know he sometimes is not sane.
Then tell Boran to listen carefully.
A horse of the man whose Bey
does not run ahead will never run.
The state of a Bey who only
gives orders from his chair
and does not go to battle
will certainly be powerless.
Whether we are Beys or Sultans, we will
never forget why we came to this world.
It is our duty to fight the
infidels on the battlefield.
Yes my Bey.
Aykurt.
My Bey, the caravan is approaching.
Let them come.
We will not harm the Alps.
You will arrest all of them.
Yes my Bey.
Come on Alps!
Come on
What is happening here?
Alps!
Attack!
Ya Allah
Kneel
What is happening?
You will pay for this!
We are the ones who will make...
...others pay, Sancar. Know that.
The price for working with traitors is death...
...but you should thank Osman Bey.
My Bey, the caravan is filled with mine!
What does this mean, Osman Bey?
Raiding the caravan of Karesi Bey...
Do you think you can get away with this?
You sold the mine that would
be swords for the Alps, huh?
You will have no place
to rest in either world.
Are we going to ask you what to sell to whom?
How can you even question Karesi Bey, Osman?
Shut up
What are you saying?
Hear your own words!
You are talking to Osman Bey!
Where is your Bey?
Why can't I see him?
You don't even see
how small you are but you
raid our caravan, and
then you ask me questions.
What do you think you are doing?
Here...
I am the Bey, and I am the state.
I do not ask questions.
I call everyone to account.
Now..
Go and tell your Bey.
I have his spy Begum Hatun.
Now, this caravan is mine.
Come on now.
Go and tell him that Osman Bey started the war.
Now..
Start running away...
...and tell your Bey what you saw. Go now!
Alaeddin. -My Bey.
Be careful.
The fuse is lit now.
From now on, the war will begin.
-Yes my Bey.
-Come on!
They are close. They are coming.
Oghuz. -My Bey.
We have reached the
frontiers that Ilbay mentioned.
But we could not see anything.
They must be around here somewhere.
But where?
Holofira
Alps!
Kill all of them! Come on
That traitor dog was going to inform them.
It can't be a coincidence that they are here.
Apparently, they are guarding the temple.
Turhan.
Hide the bodies of these dogs.
Yes my Shahzade.
-Oghuz. -My Bey.
Bring the horses.
-Yes my Shahzade.
My Holofira... You are alright, huh?
-I am alright.
Come on Alps! Come on
I have waited a long time for this day.
I will finally see the enemies I
have heard about from my aunt.
I have always imagined it.
If they are bad enough to
kill my mother and father...
...then they are as ugly as that, aren't they?
Or terrifying.
Welcome, Fatma Hatun.
-May it be easy.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Osman's daughter, Fatma.
They all look beautiful.
Welcome Bala Hatun. May it be easy. Thank you.
Welcome Bala Hatun...
May Allah bless you. Welcome Bala Hatun.
Don't approach them.
We must be careful.
I will see that horrible woman. -Not now.
Praise be.
Listen to me.
She mustn't see us. Come on.
Not now, Poena
Welcome.
Welcome, Bala Hatun.
-Welcome.
-Thank you.
-Thank you, welcome.
May your work be easy.
-Thank you.
-Thank you, Bala Hatun.
-Daughter.
-Mother.
Thank you. May your work be easy.
She is beautiful.
Come on, come on.
Karesiogullari Beylic
Do I have permission, my Bey? -Come in!
My Bey.
-Yes?
Osman Bey attacked the caravan.
He got all the ores and took the alps captive.
My Bey... Sancar...
-Sancar what?
He killed Sancar too.
Is he dead?
Kanyumaz.
You...
What are you saying, Kanyumaz?
-My Bey...
Osman Bey found out about
your contact with Begum Hatun.
So he imprisoned Begum Hatun.
She will stand trial.
Osman... How did he find out?
-I don't know, my Bey.
Osman.
...will execute Begum Hatun.
Shall I inform our Beys?
Shall we gather the soldiers?
First, we will save Begum Hatun.
I will draw her on my side.
Send a message to Gencer Bey.
Tell him to take Begum Hatun away somehow.
As you order my Bey.
I will drown you in deep waters, Osman.
You will pay a heavy price for this.
You'll pay a heavy price for this.
I am... Are you alright?
I didn't see you were coming.
I'm sorry, Fatma Hatun. My mistake.
But... What will I tell my grandmother now?
I bought this with my last coin.
Don't be upset.
Wait, wait.
-What's your name?
-Meryem.
-Meryem... Did we meet before?
-No, we've moved here recently.
-I'm sorry.
-Wait. Don't be.
It wasn't your mistake.
Let's buy some molasses for you.
No, I can't accept this. It was my mistake.
No way. I accept no objections. Let's go.
-May your work be easy.
-Thank you, Bala Hatun.
There my mother comes.
Even if you object to
me, you can't object to her.
-Another time, Fatma Hatun.
-Stop. Wait.
I owe you one, alright?
My daughter, come here.
-Mother.
Not now. It's too crowded.
Not now. Let's go.
Come on.
This is Sofia's nest, my Shahzade.
It's protected like a castle.
Their den will be their hell, of course.
But first...
...we need to be sure
that this is Sofia's place.
My Shahzade, someone's coming.
Stop!
Search the cart.
Only women can pass. Men have to wait.
Open the gate.
You can go.
I was planning to enter
disguising as priests...
...but they let only women in.
I will go alone.
-They won't notice anything.
-That's not happening.
I can't let you go there alone.
-Orhan.
-It's out of question.
I don't want to hear
any other words.
What will we do, my Shahzade?
If this is Sofia's place,
we shouldn't scare her.
We will prepare well and rush inside.
Now we're going back to the tribe.
Let's go.
We investigated as you ordered
and we found a lead, my Bey.
Some armed people with dark clothes
are entering a monastery near Akhisar.
-They didn't see you, did they?
-No, my Bey.
We observed from a distance.
Byzantine soldiers watch at the gate, my Bey.
Nobody but Christian nuns can go inside.
They let no men in.
If it were for only nuns
..soldiers wouldn't need to watch.
Obviously, they're hiding
someone inside. They are inside.
We can get prepared and attack
the monastery at dawn, but...
...if Sofia's men aren't inside, this
will only bother Orthodox community.
You're right, girl.
That place will be our land soon.
The community of that
monastery will be our people soon.
We shouldn't break their
hearts before we are sure.
Then I will infiltrate into
the monastery first, my Bey.
A few sisters and I will
disguise as Christian nun...
...and enter the monastery
and observe around.
No.
No, Bala.
That demon may show up there.
I can't send you on such a dangerous mission.
Don't you know me, my Bey?
I can enter that monastery,
make them believe I'm...
a Christian nun and
come out of there alive.
Mother, I'm going with you then.
Let me go with you too.
They are my coreligionists. We
will draw less suspicion in this way.
You're right, my dear.
You can speak their language too. Let's go.
Gonca.
You go to Sogut.
The market shouldn't
stay without a head, alright?
Begum Hatun.
Just wait. Wait.
Do I have permission, my Bey?
-Come in!
My Bey.
Stall the sisters carrying the food.
Change this bread with the other one.
Don't draw any suspicion.
My Bey.
-Wait.
Follow Begum Hatun when she escapes.
Tell her that Karesi Bey's soldiers
are waiting for him in the north.
-Alright?
-As you order, my Bey.
I did my part.
Begum Hatun.
The rest is up to your skills.
Oguz Alp.
-Let me see my sister.
-No, Yusuf Bey.
Osman Bey gave strict orders.
-We can't let anyone in.
Brother, you're making a mistake.
My sister isn't a traitor. She
didn't betray anyone. Sister!
Do you hear me, sister?
-Yusuf Bey.
Raise no difficulties. Go now.
Okay, brother. Okay.
I'm here, sister. Don't worry. I will save you!
Don't worry. I will save you!
Don't worry
My brother...
Here is your food, Begum Hatun.
Thank you.
You didn't accept my friendship but...
...I'm still saving you from the fire.
You didn't leave me alone, huh, Karesi Bey?
You sent Kanyumaz for me.
Sisters! Alps! Come here!
Begum Hatun.
You...
-Gencer Bey's alp. My Bey has sent me.
Wear those clothes quickly.
They're waiting for you in the north.
My pretty-faced wife.
I believe in you.
But you need to be careful.
Of course, Osman. I will be.
I won't die before seeing Sofia's death.
About her last words...
Her last words? You're
thinking about the secret?
Do I have permission, my Bey?
Come in!
Begum Hatun escaped from the cage tent, my Bey.
Begum Hatun escaped, huh?
I'm not a traitor!
I know.
I know, Begum Hatun.
When Boran and Cerkutay followed
you, they heard what you told Karesi Bey.
You said you would never
take Karesi Bey's side.
-What is this situation then, my Bey?
-That's why you are here.
To draw no suspicion while
taking Karesi Bey's side.
He will attempt to save
you and you will go to him.
And you'll pledge loyalty.
When he works with the heathens
...you will inform me.
When your betrayal is exposed
...the real traitor will feel easy. So...
...he will make a mistake.
And?
As you ordered, I got all the
beys and their men followed.
The one who helped Begum Hatun escape...
-Who?
Gencer, my Bey.
Gencer, huh?
Do I have permission, my Bey?
-Come in!
My Bey, this is Gencer Bey's alp.
We made him speak. He confessed everything.
-Take him to the square.
-As you order, my Bey.
It's you, huh?
We will see now.
What are we waiting for? The traitor escaped!
What will we tell Osman Bey now?
Let's go after Begum Hatun!
-Bayhan Bey.
Calm down. Our alps are
following her. Don't worry.
Besides
...nobody will step out of the tribe
without Osman Bey's permission.
My sister isn't a traitor! She
never betrayed Osman Bey!
But I don't know why she escaped.
Escaping would mean accepting the disgrace.
-Why, sister?
-Yusuf.
You said it yourself.
Escaping means accepting the guilt.
Now it's halal for all of
us to kill Begum Hatun!
Attention! Osman Bey!
Betrayal...
...will be punished, of course.
Although Begum Hatun escaped,
...the one who helped her
escape is among us now.
Leave me! Osman Bey! What are you doing?
Betrayal...
...is performed secretly.
But it never stays secret.
What, Gencer Bey?
Did you think I wouldn't find
out you were working with Karesi?
I didn't betray you, Osman Bey.
-Shut up!
Shut up!
You keep telling lies by looking into my eyes.
About the hunt
...you told Karesi everything I planned.
You helped Sofia escape from us.
I started this path taking the risk of death.
You knew that.
You knew that but still you betrayed me.
And also
...you helped Begum
Hatun escape from the tribe.
Gencer Bey.
You disobeyed my orders.
You violated our laws.
You betrayed the state.
My Bey.
I made a mistake, but forgive me.
Don't kill me, my Bey. -No.
Bring him. -My Bey... My Bey...
You didn't just betray me...
...you betrayed the state.
Osman Bey...
...might forgive.
But the state...
...the state never forgives.
The state..
...always makes the traitors pay for it.
Gencer Bey.
You betrayed your Bey...
...our laws...
...and our state.
Now, the price for this is death.
I worship except Allah and I bear witness that
Muhammad(PBUH) is His servant and Messenger.
Divine justice has been served, Osman Bey.
Thanks to Allah, justice has
been served, Osman Bey.
This fallen head...
...is not the first, nor will it
be the last traitor among us.
Let everyone hear that...
...anyone who tries to do this again...
...will face the same fate.
Poena.
Did you see your enemies?
Have you met Bala?
I feel so bad, aunt.
I saw them.
I saw Bala, her daughter.
What happened? Tell me.
They stole my family, my life.
They killed my mother and father.
But they are still very happy. Is this fair?
No.
But you and I will bring
justice, my little bird.
They will pay for all the pain they caused us.
You will...
...take the revenge...
...of your mother and father.
Don't cry.
It's time for revenge.
Tell me.
How was your first day on the mission?
I met Osman's daughter, Fatma.
I saw Bala.
How did you...
..feel when you..
...first saw her?
Wrath
I wanted to kill her...
...right there.
Poena.
Soon...
...very soon, you will kill her.
Karacaogullari Beylic
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in.
We brought Begum Hatun here safely, my Bey.
Thanks to Allah.
We saved you from Osman's hands safely.
As you order, my Bey.
Thank you Karesi Bey.
Thanks to you, I can see
what is right and wrong very well.
I told you.
Osman is very skilled at executing
people with extreme prejudice.
He lives far from justice
and is unaware of our laws.
You are right.
He didn't even let me speak or defend myself.
He was going to take me to the gallows.
They have done you wrong so many times.
From now on, you are with me.
Osman can never touch you.
Never.
But we must strengthen this with our union.
What do you mean, Karesi Bey?
I don't want your
allegiance, Begum Hatun.
Then..
...what do you want from me? Why..
...did you save me, Karesi Bey?
Begum Hatun...
I want to marry you.
Marry me.
Karesi Bey.
Be my wife in my house.
Be my companion on my path...
...and be the Hatun of my Beylic.
What do you think?
Yes...
...or no?
I don't know what to say.
Osman Bey.
I mean, Osman Bey will pay for it for sure.
I accept marrying you, Karesi Bey.
Kanyumaz.
My Bey.
Forty rams will be sacrificed.
Gifts should be given to forty doors.
Set a full table.
We will celebrate tomorrow.
Send news to our Beys.
Come on! -As you say, my Bey!
Scholar...
Be careful.
Don't upset yourself for
anything Trickster Hatun.
Attention! Osman Bey!
My Bala.
Now I am going to question Karesi Bey for this.
And you will go and see if
Sofia's men are in the monastery.
But don't make a move before I come.
Don't worry my Bey.
Come on, children! We will leave first!
-Is our gift ready?
-Yes my Bey.
It was prepared with care
for Karesi Bey, my Bey.
We won't go empty-handed even to Karesi Bey,
who shows a friendly face and bears hostility.
It is our tradition.
Of course, we'll go there with our gift.
Kayi is both the hammer and the anvil.
We will show Karesi Bey that.
To horses!
Do you really have to see Lukas and
Sofia and trade with them Karesi Bey?
They tried to kill my brother.
I know.
They will apologize to you for this.
And they will do it today.
I invited them for dinner.
Don't be upset...
In the end, you are the Hatun of Karesi Beylic.
Who can stand against you?
Besides...
...we will be stronger thanks to
our alliance with Lukas and Sofia.
Osman will eventually kneel before us.
I guess this will not be an eternal alliance.
I always consider my own
interests, Begum Hatun.
I will use Lukas and Sofia...
...and soon, I will throw them away.
Come here.
From now on, half of my
ships will be under your control.
Also...
...as a wedding gift...
...the most glorious one
of my castles will be yours.
Thank you Karesi Bey.
Live long.
I haven't forgotten your brother Yusuf either.
I will let him be the Commander of my armies.
He must be mad at me right now.
But he will understand me for sure.
He will learn what his sister has sacrificed.
Karesi Bey is marrying Begum Hatun.
Begum Hatun?
She was very loyal to Osman.
It seems she loves Karesi more.
He invites us to the celebration meal.
We will go to that meal, Lukas.
To strengthen our alliance with Karesi Bey.
We will go there.
Wait, you can't come in.
Open the door.
Come in.
Mother...
Mother what happened?
Mother?
What happened? Are you alright?
Mother...
Are you alright?
I am alright.
I am alright, my daughter.
Let's take a look around.
It will be necessary for our move.
As we thought, my daughter...
This is Sofia's nest.
Her soldiers are here.
This place is well hidden.
But we solved their secret, thank Allah.
Come on.
My Beys.
Hatuns.
On this happy day of mine, you
accepted our invitation and came.
You have shared our meal.
-Live long.
-Thank you.
This feast..
...is in honor of my future wife, Begum
Hatun, who has expanded my home and palace...
...by joining our side.
Her presence will...
...give strength to both me
and our state, God willing.
God willing, my Bey.
Thank you, Karesi Bey.
It is an honor for me to be under the same
roof and in the same gathering with you.
-Thank you.
Then, enjoy your meal.
My Bey, Osman Bey came.
Alps, let him in.
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
Come, Osman, come.
You've heard that
I am marrying Begum Hatun...
...and even brought a gift.
Right.
Have you married Begum Hatun?
Someone like you, who betrays
her state would only deserve this man.
Osman, you came to my castle and now...
...are insulting me and my future
wife in the presence of my Beys!
I am!
I call a traitor a traitor
and a treacher a treacher.
Karesi Bey.
So that the Beys are here...
...they should all hear it.
Let them all hear the
treachery you have committed.
Beys.
Tell me.
This careless man...
...whom you call a ruler and stand behind...
...sold the steel of the swords
that would kill our Alps...
...to infidels!
-Karesi Bey would never do that.
-He did it.
He did it.
This careless man you stand behind...
Shame on you
Osman... Enough! -No!
No, Karesi Bey!
Wait...
Boran. -My Bey.
Take this to Karesi Bey.
No.
Put it next to him, right next to him.
Open it, Karesi Bey.
Open it.
Open it!
-How could you do this, Osman!
-This!
An eye for an eye..
...a tooth for a tooth!
So...
...you sent this traitor to our side, huh?
Here is his head.
Now, I have the decree! You...
...that traitor, and everyone behind you...
Now...
Now we are all in war with you.
Did you think you could come
here and leave this place alive?
Osman
My Bey!
Alps!
Kill all of them
You draw a sword against me? Come to me.
What you have done is enough!
Alps, stop! Stop, stop.
We will get out just like
how we got inside.
Alps!
Kanyumaz.
Catch him.
Move.
-Tell them to clear the way.
-Move aside. Come on!
Move.
Move aside!
Run with my call.
This will reinforce your
credibility for Karesi.
Alps, stop!
Lower the spears!
Now.
You will pay for what you did, Osman Bey!
But not now. Karesi Bey is
wounded. Let's go, Kanyumaz.
-Orhan.
-Mother.
We've found Sofia's nest. Soldiers are inside.
-Thanks to Allah.
-They are too many.
When my Bey arrives,
...we will destroy them all, God willing.
God willing.
We should wait now. They shouldn't see us.
My lady, some Turks have
been detected around the temple.
-Poena...
They may be making a game.
Soldiers, we're going to
the temple now! Come on!
This is enough. Stop.
Very soon
...I will bring the death to those
barbarians who slaughtered my family.
Bala, what is the situation?
My Bey, this is Sofia's place. We're sure now.
All her men are inside, my Bey.
But there are priestesses
and women inside, my Bey.
Dastards are hiding behind them.
When we enter the temple,
we'll kill all Sofia's men.
But, my girl, you will take priestesses
and women somewhere safe.
As you order, my Bey.
Boran and Cerkutay are lying
in ambush around the temple.
When we attack, Sofia
won't get any news about it.
We'll attack the temple and Sofia will
come to us without knowing anything.
We'll just wait for our prey, huh, my Bey?
Absolutely.
We'll hunt her in her own place.
Bala, my daughter. You go to
the gate and provide security there.
May Allah bless our fight!
-Aameen.
Let's go, girl.
Open this! Hurry up!
Open this!
I should take Poena out
before they know everything
Open! Open
We'll arrive in time, Sofia.
Before they know everything,
...I should take Poena out.
Come on.
Come on!
Come on
I made a monster out of Poena.
If Osman gets her,
...everything will be ruined.
He won't, Sofia.
That monster will be their death.
Come this way.
Nobody will hurt you.
This way, come on.
-Behind you.
-You got this.
Osman.
-Osman!
-You got this.
Bala.
Bala!
Let's go.
-Brother!
-Alaaddin!
Orhan and Alaaddin.
Their children.
Come on, brother!
Today is the day of vengeance.
You will pay for what I suffered!
Die!
Swing your swords and break the demon's army!
You will die for your family, Osman.
Osman
Aunt.
-I'm here!
Take Poena out of here!
This temple you stained with your steps
will be cleaned with your blood, Osman.
You demon's dog. Your dirt
can be cleaned only in hell.
Sofia.
Let's unseal your tongue.
You remember, huh?
I will kill you not once but a thousand times.
Then tell me now. Or you will just pass away.
Aunt.
You're dead
You're a dead man, Osman.
You can't run away this time.
Come.
Osman
Father!
My Bey!
Die.